

Daniel Denton

Los Angels, CA

(323)363-3279 • daniel@danieldentondev.com

<u>LinkedIn</u> • <u>Portfolio</u> • <u>GitHub</u>



Software Developer with 2+ years of experience in mobile-app full-stack development as lead sole developer responsible for the full techstack at technology startup where I led product cycle from conception to launch and support.

Relevant Experience

Software Engineer • PainNavigator • Chicago IL • 2022-Present

- Lead sole developer for the company, acting as Head of Technology, managing all new features and functionality and maintaining the existing codebase using React Native/Ruby on Rails stack
- Work directly with the CEO, translating high level requirements into new features, making all technical decisions, while considering user experience and scalability.
- Leveraged the Ruby on Rails framework to build a provider dashboard web app for clients to monitor their patients' live progress, as well as an administration dashboard and live chat web application for in-app messaging.
- Manage all DevOps tasks, including deployment on the App Store and Google Play Store.
- Monitor and handle incident response for the mobile app and server.
- Created the test suite using Jest and React Native Testing Library.

Electronic Engineer • Wren & Cuff • Newbury Park CA • 2020-2022

- Assembled and repaired various guitar effects working off physical and digital diagrams.
- Quality control and testing of all products to ensure meeting company standards before going to market.
- Assessed damaged merchandise to make recommendations on best outcome.

Education

General Assembly • Software Engineering Immersive • Remote • Jan 2022 - April 2022

Skills

React, React Native, NextJS, Typescript, Javascript, Node, ExpressJS, Firebase, Ruby on Rails, Python, Django, SQL, MongoDB, Solidity, EthersJS, Expo Go, Heroku, App Store, Google Play Store

References

- Kelly McKay, CEO of PainNavigator, kelly@painnavigator.io (805) 448-0632
- Matthew Holl, Owner of Wren and Cuff, matthew@wrenandcuff.com (818) 472-0632

Additional experience and references available upon request